

Nur Awwabin Yoga Saputra

Backend Developer

Experienced Backend Developer adept in all stages of advanced backend developer. Knowledgeable TDD, logic, and debugging processes. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Proficient assortment of technologies, including Laravel, Express JS, Oauth2, JWT, Lumen, MySql, and Postgree SQL. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

+6285156790119 | Blora, Central Java, Indonesia

CONTACT INFO

yogasaputran@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/nurays

https://github.com/Yoga-Saputra

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

University of Amikom Yogyakarta(GPA: 3.54)

Bachelor Degree | 2016 - 2019 | Computer Science

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Jquery
- MySQL
- PostgreeSQL VPS
- GIT
- Javascript
- Scrum
- Postman

- PHP
- Laravel
- Livewire
- Lumen
- Express JS
- Digitalocean
- Rest API
- JWT
- Repository Pattern

LANGUAGES

- English
- Indonesia

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

Feb 2020 - Aug, 2020

- Build Qasir App using laravel 6
- Database MySQL
- Deploy to VPS
- Create CI/CD (github action)

Laravel Developer

PT. Koding Teknologi Asia| Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

- Build system management member using laravel 6
- Deploy to shared hosting
- Database MySQL

ENGINERING TECHNICAL PROVICIENCY

- Have knowledge about scrum master.
- Fast learning and having good analytical thinking.
- Able to use version control system(VCS) by using GIT.
- Good knowledge of relational database
- Able to work independently as well as in team
- Problem solving
- Able to implement swagger in laravel project

RELEVANT COURSES

- Devops at Build With Angga May 2022 - June 2022
- Web Development Microservices at Build With Angga March 2022 - Present
- Fullstack Web Developer at Build With Angga
 Jan 2022 - Present

WORK EXPERIENCE

Laravel Developer

Phicos : Ideas for IT Solutions | Mar, 2021 - Aug, 2021

Freelance Web Developer

Nov, 2020 - May 2022

- Build Website System Absen for Government Using Laravel 6
- Database MySQL
- Deploy to VPS (digitalocean)
- Create CI/CD (github action)
- Maintenance

Backend Developer

Cikatech | Jun, 2021 - May, 2022

- Create rest api using Laravel and Express JS
- Fixing bug
- Custome jwt for authenticate
- Collaborate with frontend dev
- Collaborate with devops
- Collaborate with QA
- Collaborate with Database Enginer